tomorrow another one will be icsl
Lombard which will be reporting numbers
today subi is here with the key
expectation survey
thanks for that so ICC Lombard is going
to come up with this Q4 Results post
market today and it is expected to be a
mixed bag the gdpi which is the gross
direct premium income is expected to be
up by 11 on a Euro year on year basis
but sequentially is going to be lower
due to the selldown in the motor
third-party portfolio our poll suggests
that net earned premium is going to be
up 21 on a year-on-year basis at 377
crores Pat is also expected to grow on
similar growth rate of 21 the combined
ratio is expected to stay at elevated
levels which is in line with what the
management has been guiding for the past
few quarters it is expected to be at 105
percent versus 103 same time last year
other than that the claim ratio is
likely to see an improvement on a full
year basis we will also watch out for
any commentary on pricing and the
distributor payout front
well keep an eye out on those numbers
thanks a lot for that uh survey well uh